All right. So, hopefully you had some fun
好的希望你在完成这个
going through and trying to complete this notebook.
Notebook 的过程中找到了乐趣
Now, let's take a look at my solutions.
下面看看我的解决方案
To start with, the first four steps are things that
前四步
we've looked at before in previous notebooks.
已经在之前的 Notebook 中讲解过
So, I've executed those cells in advance.
我提前执行了这些单元格
At this point, we have an XGBoost model that has been trained
目前 我们已经有一个训练过的 XGBoost 模型
and which we tested and seems to be performing pretty well.
我们测试了该模型 效果不错
So, the story at this point is that,
所以目前我们的 XGBoost 模型
our XGBoost model is good enough that we want to put it in production.
效果很好 可以部署到生产环境了
So, we've deployed it somewhere and it is being used by some application.
我们部署了该模型 某个应用正在使用它
Over time, we collect some reviews from users
之后 我们从用户那收集了一些影评
and we create ground truths for those reviews.
并为这些影评创建了真实情感结果
We could maybe do this by hand,
我们可以手动创建
or find some other mechanism to do that.
也可以采用其他机制
But regardless, we've collected a bunch of
无论如何 我们收集了大量样本影评
these sample reviews and we'd like to see how well our model is performing.
并且想要看看模型的效果如何
This is a part of health checking our model essentially.
也就是检查模型的运行状况
So, we load in the new data.
我们加载了新的数据
The first thing we do is encode our new data
首先对新数据进行编码
so that we can send it off to our XGBoost model.
从而能够将其发送给 XGBoost 模型
Remember that the processing that we'd perform on a review is in two parts.
我们对影评的处理分成两部分
First, we stem our input so that things like hunting and hunt appear as the same token.
第一部分是词干化处理 例如 使 hunting 和 hunt 变成同一个分词
Then, we look at the 5,000 most frequently occurring words in the training set,
第二部分是查看训练集中出现频率在前 5,000 的字词
we call that our vocabulary.
称之为词汇表
Then, for each review,
然后对于每条影评
we count the number of times each word in our vocabulary
我们都计算词汇表中的每个字词出现在该影评中的次数
occurs and we store that vector of length equal to the vocabulary.
并将次数存储到向量中 该向量的长度等于词汇表的大小
In our case it's 5,000,
对我们来说是 5,000
as the bag of words encoded version of our review.
并作为影评的词袋编码
Now, our new data has already been tokenized.
现在 新数据已经标记化
However, we still need to create a bag of words encoding of it.
但是 需要创建词袋编码
To do that, we create
我们使用
a count vectorizer object using
在之前的 notebook 中
the vocabulary that we created earlier on in the notebook.
创建的词汇表创建一个 CountVectorizer 对象
We want to make sure that there's no extra preprocessing or extra tokenizing happening.
这一步是为了确保不再预处理或额外标记化字词
Once we've created that count vectorizer,
创建了 CountVectorizer 对象后
we can use it to transform the new data to
我们可以使用它转换新数据
get the vectorized or bag of words encoded version of our data.
获得数据的向量化或词袋编码版本
As a quick check that this transform operation did what we expect that it did,
为了快速检查下这个转换操作的行为是否符合预期
we should double-check and make sure that any of the rows in
我们应该再次检查下
our new data set have length equal to the size of our vocabulary.
新数据集中的任何一行长度是否等于词汇表的大小
In our case, the vocabulary size is 5,000.
我们的词汇表大小是 5,000
So, the length of each of the reviews should be 5,000, which it is.
所以每条影评的长度应该是 5,000 的确是
Okay. Now, our goal here is to test our model to see how well it's doing on the new data.
Ok我们的目标是测试模型 看看它在新数据上的效果
So, to do that, we're going to set up
我们将设置一个批转换作业
a batch transform job and in order to execute a batch transform job,
为了执行批转换作业
we need to first,
我们首先需要
save the new data locally into a CSV file,
将新数据保存到本地 CSV 文件中
and then we need to upload that CSV file to S3 using the upload data method.
然后使用 upload_data 方法将该 CSV 文件上传到 S3
Once your data has been uploaded and is available on S3,
将数据上传到 S3 后
we can go ahead and use the transformer object that was created
我们可以使用之前创建的 transformer 对象
earlier and transform our new data to see how well our model is performing.
并转换新数据 看看模型的效果如何
Once the transform job has finished up,
转换作业运行完毕后
we can copy the results to our local instance and then
我们将结果复制到本地实例中
check to see how well our model is performing on the new data.
然后看看模型在新数据上的效果
Oh, it turns out not so great.
结果不太理想
So, something has gone wrong here.
出问题了
I think that a reasonable explanation is that
我认为合理的解释是
something has happened to the underlying distribution.
底层分布发生了变化
So, that is that the words in our new data set don't mean
新数据集中的字词与原始数据集的含义不太一样
the same thing or aren't being encoded as well as they were in the original data set.
或者编码效果不如原始数据集
So, what can we do to try and look and see what's happening here?
该如何检查发生的问题呢？